{
    "id": "76173d3dc38a4a9fb3786f0d83014fa1",
    "title": "Gap Fills",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Would you rather ……………………. here or go home?",
            "description": "Would rather is followed by an infinitive without to. ",
            "answers": [
                "to stay",
                "stay",
                "staying"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "78b8d84467854e04bcffcdd28ea61146"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would rather you …………………………. now.",
            "description": "To say that you would prefer someone to do something, we use a past tense after would rather.",
            "answers": [
                "leave",
                "left",
                "have left"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d8081e29b3144d7399aa816046671bbf"
        },
        {
            "question": "I decided to phone rather than …………………………",
            "description": "When the main clause has a to-infinitive, rather than is usually followed by an infinitive without to. Ing forms are also possible.",
            "answers": [
                "write",
                "writing",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "32d7631fe6f64ee1b946273de8596450"
        },
        {
            "question": "She took her child with ………………………..",
            "description": "The reflexive pronoun is unusual after a preposition of place.",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "herself",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "799aa6e35fa242a29fd1f348eac58a31"
        },
        {
            "question": "Would you mind if I ………………………… the window?",
            "description": "A past tense is used after would you mind.",
            "answers": [
                "open",
                "opened",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d5256da25aab4fc6a9b2dd1a1e525324"
        },
        {
            "question": "Would you mind if I ……………………….. late?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "come",
                "came",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1726c2299dfa4ac2abf4cfed76d3020f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you mind if I ………………………. music?",
            "description": "A present tense is used after do you mind.",
            "answers": [
                "play",
                "played"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a55134b58bd441108240ae70228095ec"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you mind people ……………………….. in your room?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "smoke",
                "smoking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0814957992c4426985f1cf6e81683594"
        },
        {
            "question": "Would you mind ………………………… people smoked in your house?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "that",
                "whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1eba124584d0412199bce50715ff3244"
        },
        {
            "question": "A new ………………………….. of communication was developed in the 19th century.",
            "description": "Means is always used in the plural form.",
            "answers": [
                "mean",
                "means"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d048622a557d4eb493a2ede2a1eb531e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wouldn’t mind ……………………….. this again.",
            "description": "An ing form is used in this structure. ",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "to do",
                "doing"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5a0c63a320e44448bd9f2dc53a16e79f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I hope ………………………… them soon.",
            "description": "An infinitive is used after I hope.",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "seeing",
                "to see"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2f796574558c42598cb19f684e3d32c3"
        }
    ]
}